Last time, Boss Luffy and company entered a once-in-a-lifetime event,
the Great Portable Shrine Race.
The grand prize is a sacred treasure
passed down through many generations in Grand Japan.
Ah!
While preparing for the big event,
they met Brook, a friendly skeleton who suffered from memory loss.
Spirits were high among all the races
until their portable shrines were destroyed
by Hogback of the Thriller Company,
a group bent on claiming the prize for themselves.
It's over!
There's no way we can enter the big race now!
And it was such a beautiful shrine, too!
If their plan was to wipe out all the portable shrines
before the race,
then that means ours is in danger, too!
I remember what happened.
You got your memory back?
Yes.
I remember everything now.
Hey, what's with the hat and that get-up?
Because it looks like you're leaving.
I shouldn't be here with you,
from what I remember.
And I'm ashamed to say this.
I believe that I'm actually a member
of the Thriller Company.
And so, with his memory suddenly returned,
Brook disappeared into the dark of night all alone.
Feudal-era side story.
Defeat Thriller Company's trap.
That was a pretty good rampage tonight, guys.
Agreed.
And I think Peronis almost should be quite pleased.
Who are you?
Every one of you has strayed from the path of humanity.
Not that you were human, to begin with.
And now, in the name of heaven,
I shall punish you!
There.
That should do it.
Thanks, buddy.
I couldn't stop him from destroying the portable shrine.
The race is tomorrow, too.
I'm a failure as a carpenter.
You gave it your best.
You didn't do a thing wrong.
Hogback and his Thriller Company cronies
are to blame for this.
Hmm.
And then there's Brook.
Yeah, I'm worried.
Any idea where he went?
Would you like me to tell you?
Hmm?
Who are you?
Just a city girl who happened to be passing by.
She's beautiful!
You would think so, huh?
Though the skeleton was indeed once a member of the Thriller Company,
he grew sick of its despicable ways
and eventually left the organization.
As far as where he went,
I'm sure he feels partially responsible
for the shrines that were destroyed today
and is likely keeping to himself.
Boss Luffy,
members of the Pinwheel Eatery,
I will make amends
for how I have lived and who with.
Wait, Boss!
Hold on!
He never thinks these things through.
Brook, I'm here!
Where are you?
Fuss, fuss, fuss, fuss, fuss, fuss,
ridiculous fool.
Uh, uh, uh,
get hurt?
Ah!
Ho ho!
Shut up!
I never thought you'd still be alive
after all of that.
The stabbings and arrow wounds
and sending you down the river
for your ugly little betrayal, I mean.
Why risk what little life you have
by coming back?
There's no point trying to explain it.
People like you would never understand.
All right then, add another weight.
I take another weight.
Yaaaaa!
Show some dignity!
That's enough!
Finish him off.
Grr.
Wait!
Hold on, time out!
I, I'm not ready to die just yet!
Grr.
Although, I have already been dead a long time.
Ho ho ho ho ho!
Aaaa!
I don't want this!
Grr!
Would you just shut up, please?
Roar!
Boss Luffy!
What's the big idea walking off like that?
Come on, let's get you back.
Not so fast!
You're that fellow we ran into earlier, the policeman!
Get out of my way!
You guys really piss me off, but I don't have any business with you right now.
Ha!
Even if you are a public official, there's no way we're letting you leave here in one piece!
Get him, boys!
You're disturbing the neighbors!
In my sleep!
Three-sword style!
Katsumaki!
A-Ru-Gum-Gum!
Go! Move it! After him!
Go!
These weirdos just keep coming!
Wait!
Where'd they...
They're gone!
They couldn't have gotten far!
Find them!
Hooray!
Hey, we're back!
My word!
Luffy!
And Brooke!
Welcome back!
I'm so glad you made it!
I'm hungry!
We've got special stamina rice balls!
Yum!
I don't understand!
What are all of you doing?
We're fixing our portable shrine, of course!
Surely not!
The race is tomorrow!
You'll never finish in time!
Don't count us out yet!
But why?
Why would you all go to such great lengths?
Our pride!
Giving up, turning tail, and running away isn't our style.
This isn't over by a long shot.
That's right!
Us two.
We all feel the exact same way.
Whoa!
It's the Rolling Express!
If you need materials, we got them!
Our portable shrine was busted up, too!
Feel free to use anything you can salvage from it!
Look at that!
The Flying Fish Riders are here, too!
We brought our busted up shrine along for the very same reason.
Use it with our gratitude!
Our spirit is in your hands now!
Oh, really?
Aw, thanks, you guys!
Ha-ha!
Ah!
Excellent!
Now I can build a super portable shrine just the way I imagined it!
Damn right we can!
Yeah, let's do it!
Looks like we've got a few more mouths to feed at dinner tonight!
I guess I should go and get started on something right now!
Sanji, dear, work hard!
You're a guard!
You got it, Mommy Swan!
I won't let you down!
Aw, come on, Brooke!
What's the matter?
This is no time to be standing around!
We need your help!
How can I ever face you all knowing that I-
Aw, come on already!
Wait, not the face!
Please!
Aw!
Aw, we gotta get this thing ready!
You're gonna be one of the shrine bearers, you know!
Do I have to spell it out for you?
He's saying that you're our friend!
I am?
Mm-hmm!
Thank you so very much!
It means the world to me!
Mm-hmm!
Stop!
There are no free meals around here!
Do you understand me?
Mm-hmm!
Okay!
Oh!
I know!
Why don't I play us a song?
It might help liven things up a bit!
Ah!
That's great!
Keep it going!
Right!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Whoa!
What in the heck is that?
It's huge!
It's a monster!
None of the other teams stand a chance against that massive thing!
He thinks of the other teams competing!
And I think it would be hilarious if they dragged their wrecked shrines out here!
Fast!
We won't have long to wait!
All we have to do is get this jumbo portable shrine across the finish line and then the treasure
will be ours!
Sindri, please, must you always stand right in front of me?
The noon hour is nigh!
Can we just skip to the victory parade now?
Please, wait just a moment!
The Pinwheel Eatery will also be participating!
No way!
Hey, Thriller Company!
We're here to win!
That treasure is ours!
Yay!
Go Team Pinwheel!
Ha!
Whatever you say, good luck with that!
Although we'd hope for a bigger turnout, allow me to introduce the two competitors for
the Great Shrine Race all the same!
The Thriller Company!
And the Pinwheel Eatery!
The first team to cross the finish line will be the winner!
Mountainader Noises
Mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo!
Mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-po-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-??
Out of the way!
Ah!
I'm blind! I can't see!
This is no time for jokes!
They've taken the lead!
Hey! My flying fish!
Keep curling it!
Me!
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast!
Sorry, this thing is really heavy, master!
You feeble imbeciles!
They're gonna catch up to us!
Stay calm, everyone!
This is the genius hog-backed shrine!
It's got a trick or two up its sleeve!
Eh.
Oh, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast!
What?
Stand out, suckas!
What the? How's he doing that?
Don't sweat it, bro. I wouldn't be the master
if I didn't hook this shrine up with some tricks of its own.
Huh?
Hey, boss, pour this coal in the shrine's mouth, okay?
Catch!
Right.
Open wide.
Everyone, hop on board the shrine!
Here we go!
Oh, no!
Hey, that's against the rule!
Yeah, like you're one to talk!
Are these really portable shrines anymore?
Someone stop this infernal jostling!
Don't worry, I'll handle it!
Try this on for size!
Uh, that's a cannon!
So, it's like that, huh?
Boss, there you have it!
Victory is finally ours!
Oh, no!
Look!
Take us to the finish, support panel!
Hardcore, too much press!
I think I like you better that way!
Hey, guys!
Just keep moving along the river!
It's a quicker route than going on land!
Right! Got it!
Now they're mine!
After them, attack!
Crap!
There's just no end to these jerks!
I was counting on something like this!
If you've got a way to help us, do it!
Uh-huh!
Keep this thing steady for me, all right?
Careful, you'll bite your tongue off!
Shut up!
36 caliber Phoenix!
Look up there!
It's the Grand Shrine!
Boss, this is the last of the cola!
Right! Got it!
I'll show them!
Activate!
Look!
The finish line!
Yeah!
Go!
Whoa!
You've gotta be kidding.
Is that the portable shrine's final form?
Foosh!
Munchie! Munchie!
That's one hell of a spider.
I commend you for forcing me to use my tramp card.
However, this is the end!
Spider-Sticky Nuts!
Damn, we're super stuck.
Come on, can't you do something?
Get us out of this.
Well, I do have one last trick up my sleeve.
I'm all out of cola.
Wait, cola?
Onami-san, down there.
This is as far as you go.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Whoa! Munchie, munchie, munchie, munchie!
Aaah!
Boss Luffy!
Catch!
Don't turn it!
Fire!
Whee!
This can't be!
Hang on to something!
Where in the hell did Sidri go at a time like this?
See a burning dose!
Let's discuss this!
Everyone was looking forward to this festival and this race and you ruined it!
So now you're gonna pay!
But I don't wanna!
And that makes the winner Pinwheel Eatery!
Congratulations. Now about the prize.
I know, it's one million Rio Berries!
Sorry, but I'm going to have to keep this.
Huh?
Your racing left this town in a state of disaster.
No fair!
Never fear.
Huh?
Just as was promised, the sacred treasure in the temple is yours.
All right!
Way to go, guys.
I wonder what the sacred treasure is like.
It's been 100 years since the shrine was last opened,
so this will be my first time seeing it as well.
This is the magical sacred treasure
passed down in Grand Japan
generation after generation
for this day!
Huh?
Instructions for the maiden panties.
Make a wish with these panties on and that wish will be granted forthwith.
Again, you must be wearing them.
Wait, limited to beautiful women only?
They're just perfect!
Oh, Mao-san.
Would you mind putting on those wish-making panties for me?
Wait, who am I?
What's going on here?
It looks like Brooks lost his memory again!
Brooks-san, I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
Well, far from Zappa Odi by Kuma's strange power,
Luffy finds himself on an unfamiliar island.
After an unfortunate bunny with some poisonous mushrooms,
he falls unconscious.
Gravely ill, he is approached by a team of female warriors
who could be friend or foe.
On the next One Piece,
landing the all-female island Amazon Lily!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!